IBRAHIM MOHAMED

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+20 112 153 2329

mondok22008@gmail.com



https://mondok25.github.io/



Giza, Egypt

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Microsoft Excel

Google Docs

EDUCATION

High School Diploma

Alkhalil Language Schools

2022-Present

A student in Alkhalil Language Schools, on my way to obtain the High School Diploma.

PROFILE

A professional front-end web developer. Bringing more than 5 years of experience leading website design projects, including gathering user requirements, producing code, creating mock ups and enhancing designs. Focused on creating clean, robust code with exceptional security. Achieves compatibility targets while meeting and exceeding customer demands, as well as having an excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction. Hardworking and passionate job seeker with strong organizational skills eager to secure entry level front-end developer position. Ready to help team achieve company goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end web developer

2021 - Present Freelancer

- -Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Guided customers on project stages and iterations with input on best practices, user needs and technology capabilities.
- Performed user experience quality assurance testing to identify and remedy shortcomings.

Full-stack web developer

Mosmos Productions

2021 - Present

- · Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.
- · Reviewed code, debugged problems and corrected issues.
- · Managed development milestones from initial steps through final delivery.

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

German

CERTIFICATIONS Web development Challenger track

2022-2022

Ministry of communications and information technology of egypt 2022

